隣人部 活動記録
Neighbors Club activity report...
Today's activity: training camp at the beach.
本日の活動 海で合宿
Oof!
I can finally sit down.
ようやく座れる
Here!
私も こちらに
I'll sit here, too.
Just take one!
早く取れ
そういえば 理科は
By the way, where did Rika go?
車両の連結部を見てくると言ってました
She said she was going to check
out the train's coupling section.
連結部
Coupling section?
あ またババなのだ
The old maid again!
ククク 愚か者め
Fool. Soon I'll be playing your final requiem.
そろそろ 終焉のレクイエムを奏でよう
Draw!
ドロー
ババ引いたばい
I drew the old maid!
ざまあみろ うんこ吸血鬼め
That's what you get, poopy vampire!
これで 私の勝ちだ
Now I'm going to win!
これ
This one.
あ またババだ
The old maid again!
WANAWANA
Gutto Good hajiketeru
グッと Good 弾ける
Angai nandai hamatten jan
案外なんだい ハマってんじゃん
Hito mishiri shiteru hima ni hajimeyou!
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
"Haganai"
クールに見えて 実は超寂しい
Kuuru ni miete, jitsu wa chou sabishii
(Mosou nara bai, bai, bai
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
妄想ならバイバイバイ
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Nani fujiyuu naku, dakedo tarinai
何不自由なく だけど足りない
(Riajuu kara tooi, tooi, tooi?
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Zannen doushi de atsumattara
残念同士で 集まったら
Ah- yosou ga dekinai
Ah- 予想が出来ない 展開の 地雷を踏んだ
Tenkai no jirai wo funda!
SOWASOWA
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
Koukai hyakkai shitakunaitte
後悔100回したくないって
Tsumannai puraido nante
sutekicchatte furikicchatte
つまんない プライドなんて
捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Zannen kannen shite mitara,
angai nandai hamatten jan
残念観念してみたら
案外なんだいハマってんじゃん
Butsukatte, dogimagi atte, mitsukeyou!
ぶつかって どぎまぎ合って 見つけよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
You! Sutekicchatte furikicchatte
YOU！ 捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Yes! Doudai? Doudai, sokontoko
Yes！ どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品  仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听:安少   翻译:银苹果   校对:喵儿&小草爱吃梨   时间轴&后期:亢奋的蛇
"No One Sleeps at Camp"
An hour's walk from the station?
駅から徒歩１時間もかかるとは
And no bus or taxi...
バスもタクシーもないとはな
しかたないでしょ
What'd you expect? People normally
get to their summer house by car!
別荘なんて車で行くところなんだから
Well, we're not getting any
closer just standing here...
まあ ここにいてもしかたない
Let's go.
行こう
What else can we do?
しかたないわね
Normally in a situation like this,
the faculty adviser would drive...
こういうときは普通顧問の先生が車を出してくれたりするのだが
D-Don't be ridiculous!
む 無茶言うな
Genius or not, there's no way
I could get a driver's license!
いくら私が天才で顧問の先生でも車の免許は取れるわけがないのだ
Even as your faculty advisor...
I thought you'd be out of shape
for this, but you're hanging in there.
お前 こういうの弱そうなのに 頑張るな
That's because Rika recharged
her batteries at the coupling section.
連結部で エネルギー充電しましたから
Those rough lumps of iron,
tightly screwed together...
武骨な鉄の塊同士がガッチリつながって
The whole time the train is running,
they're going squish-squish, ohhh...
走行中に ずっとギシギシアンアンやっているのですよ
What could be more erotic?!
あんなエロエロ空間はほかにないです
Just being there made Rika
feel like getting down and dirty!
あそこにいるだけで 理科までエッチな気持ちになってしまいます
あッ う 海
O-O-Ocean!
海 海 海
Ocean! Ocean! Oceaaaaaaan!
We're here!
ついたわね
The summer house is this way.
別荘はこっちよ
Is it really okay for us to use this?
ここ ホントに俺達だけで使っていいのか
Of course!
もちろんよ
I-I-I'm gonna swim! Bro, I'm gonna swim!
お お 泳ぐ あんちゃん泳ぐ
そんな興奮してお前は子供だな
Being excited like that
shows what a little kid you are!
After we put the bags inside, okay?
荷物 運んでからな
Come to think of it, aren't
we going to do that thing?
そういえばあれはやらないんですか
Thing?
あれ
Where we face the sea, strike
a pose, and yell, "The ocean!"
何かみんなでポーズとりながら海に向かって
「海だー！」って叫ぶという羞恥プレイのことです
It's humiliation play.
Don't even say "humiliation play."
羞恥プレイとか言うな
But that reminds me, they
did that in Mofu Mofu, too.
そういえば 「もふモフ！」でも
みんなで海に行ったときにそれやってたわね
I've seen that in manga before,
but what the hell is it about?
私もマンガなどで見たことはあるが あれは一体何なんだ
Is it a "happy people" ritual?
リア充の儀式か
We may be able to understand if
we become "happy people" ourselves.
リア充になれば理解できるのかもしれませんね
I don't really get it, but should we practice?
じゃあ よく分かんないけど練習しとく
Right! If we come to the
beach with friends in the future
そうだな 将来友達と海に来る機会があったときに
and don't know how to do it, we'll be at a loss!
ちゃんとできないと困るからな
Is that really something that you practice?
あれは練習するものなのか
So we just face the sea and yell, "The ocean"?
海に向かって「海だー！」って叫ぶのか 訳が分からんな
I don't see the point...
When I give the signal,
everyone shout for all you're worth.
私が合図したらみんな一斉に叫ぶのだぞ
The pose is up to you.
ポーズは任せる
All right! Here I go!
よし ではいくぞ
One... two...
せーの
The ocean...
海だ
This salt air doesn't agree with Rika's lungs.
理科 潮風苦手です
I-I think I know what it is...
な なんかアレだな
R-Right...
そ そうね
Yeah, huh?
だよな
It's better to practice
something like this on our own.
こういうのは一人で練習するべきものだな
Let's put off group "The ocean!" yelling
practice until we've made more progress.
「海だ！」と叫ぶ練習はもうちょっと上達してからにしよう
What kind of progress?
上達って何だよ
The blue sky, white waves,
and red sun are calling to me!
青い空と白い波と真っ赤な太陽がわれを呼んでおるわ
Yay!
Kobato, no playing until you put sunblock on.
小鳩 遊ぶのはちゃんと日焼け止め塗ってからな
Your counsel is wearisome!
むッ 忠告大儀である
If I get a sunburn and
take a bath, it hurts so bad...
日焼けして お風呂に入るととても痛いからな ククク
That's cold!
冷たい
It's not gonna kill you.
我慢しろ
Bro!
何かすごくいやらしいです 先輩
That looks extremely indecent, Sempai!
You guys better get some on, too.
お前らもちゃんと塗っとけよ
I didn't bring any...
私は持ってきてないのだが
But I should be okay...
まあ 大丈夫か
Big Brother! Slap some UV barrier on me, too!
おにいちゃん 私にも紫外線バリア 塗って 塗って
Yeah, you look like you burn easily too, Maria.
おお マリアも肌弱そうだからな
Aniki, would you do it to me, too?
アニキ 私もお願いできますか
Y-Yeah, sure. After Maria...
おう 分かった マリアの次な
I'm grateful for your kindness.
恐縮です
In the meantime, I'll rub
some on your back, Aniki.
では私がアニキの後ろを
Kodaka-sempai!
Y-Y-Y-Yukimura-kun rubbing
against Kodaka-sempai's back...
ゆ ゆ 幸村くんが小鷹先輩のバックを
Even though Kodaka-sempai is a little
nervous, his heart beats fast in anticipation,
小鷹先輩はちょっぴり緊張しながらも期待に胸を高鳴らせて
as Yukimura-kun puts his unexpectedly
impressive you-know-what inside...
幸村くんの意外なほど立派なそれを受け入れ
It's so big...
すごく大きいです
Excalibur!
エクスカリバー
I don't understand...
訳が分からん
Yozora! P-Put suntan lotion on me!
夜空 あたしに日焼け止めを塗りなさい
Huh? Why should I help to process meat?
ああ 何で私が肉の加工を手伝わなければならないのだ
べ 別にいいでしょ
I-It's no big thing!
ふん まあいい 塗ってやる
Fine. I'll put it on you.
Here I go.
いくぞ
That's cold!
冷たい
Grin and bear it.
我慢しろ
Can't you put it on a little more gently?
もうちょっと丁寧に塗れないの力入れすぎじゃない
I think you're putting
too much strength into it.
That's because you're not used to it.
慣れてないからな
ふん ならしかたないわね
Then I guess it'll have to be that way...
Just make sure you get me everywhere.
ちゃんとムラなく塗りなさいよね
Sure, leave it to me.
ああ 任せておけ
Hey, do you have really big hands?
ねえ あんたの手結構大きくない
It's just your imagination.
気のせいだろう
Really? Maybe it just
feels differently on my back...
そう 背中だから感覚が違うのかしら
あんた 何やってんのよ
W-W-W-What the heck are you doing?!
Whoops. Don't get up yet.
おっと まだ起きるな
What? I-I can't move?
何 動けない
Because I'm pinning
down your center of gravity...
重心をおさえているからな
No matter how much strength you
put into it, you won't be able to get up!
どれだけ力を入れても立ち上がれまい
Exposing your back to me was stupid, Meat!
私に背中をさらすとは間抜けな肉め
Rub the lotion on with your hands, idiot!
ちゃんと手で塗りなさいよ バカ
What's the difference if I use my hands or feet?
手で塗るのも足で塗るのも変わらないだろう
There's a big difference!
大違いよ 他人の背中を踏んでもいいのはあたしだけだから
- I'm the only one who gets
to step on people's backs!
- That reminds me, it seems you reward
your male hangers-on by stepping on them.
そういえば 貴様は取り巻きの男どもをご褒美と称して踏んでいるらしいな
How's this? Are you happy with my reward?
どうだ 私のご褒美は嬉しいか
O-Of course I'm not happy, stupid Yozora!
嬉しいわけないでしょ バカ夜空
What I do is valuable because
they're the feet of a goddess!
あれは神であるあたしの足だから 価値があるのよ
I think you're actually pleased
that I'm walking on your back!
本当は貴様 踏まれて喜んでいるのではないか
Your body responds honestly!
体は正直だぞ
Th-That's not... true!
そ そんなこと ない
Looks like I was right on the money!
図星のようだな 地面に体をおしつけられて
地面に体をおしつけられて 起き上がることもできず
Having your body pushed against
the ground, unable to even get up,
stripped of your pride and
dignity, in a humiliating position,
誇りも尊厳も奪われた屈辱的な格好で
just being trampled on!
ただ 蹂躙されるがままになっている
Being pleased in a situation like
this makes you a grade-A pervert!
こんな状況を喜ぶなんて貴様はとんだ変態だな
You sow meat slave!
このメスブタ肉奴隷め
I-It doesn't feel good at all...
き 気持ちよくなんか ないのに
Finding joy in being
abused is the real you, bitch...
貴様の本質は虐げられることに喜びを見いだすメス犬
You're a born pervert, Meat!
生まれながらの変態肉なのだ
You're a mucus-covered
walking obscenity, girl meat!
動くわいせつ物
粘液まみれのメス肉め
Say, " Please trample me into
the sand as much as you like!"
思う存分 めちゃくちゃに蹂躙してくださいと
Beg for mercy from me, your goddess!
神であるこの私に慈悲を乞え
- Don't push... your luck!
- What?!
調子に乗るな
何
I-I'm not a pervert!
あたしは変態なんかじゃないんだから
I'm a queen and a goddess! Got it?!
私こそが女王様で女神なんだからね 分かった
Honestly, you're saucy, Meat!
まったく 生意気な肉だ
Oh! Sena's boobs are big, aren't they?!
星奈はオッパイ大きいな
Damn you, Yozora, you evil slime!
夜空のド畜生外道スライムー
You're the one who's covered in slime.
ふん スライムは貴様だろうが
Idiot!!
バカ
Even at the beach, she gets like this...
海でも結局こうなるのか あいつは
There!
そーれ
Nice!
Got it!
Okay...
There!
I'm the only one who can cook?
料理できんの俺だけかよ
Was there yogurt?
ヨーグルトあったかな
What are you doing here?
何やってんだ こんなとこで
K-Kodaka...
こ 小鷹
D-Did you, um...
あ あんた あのその
み 見た
...see that?
S-See what?
何を
Before I ran away, um...
私が走ってく前に その
I was putting sunblock on Kobato
then, so I'm not sure what you mean,
あのときは 小鳩に日焼け止め塗ってたから よく知らねえけど
but I bet Yozora was
teasing you again, wasn't she?
どうせ また夜空にいびられたんだろ
Yeah! Th-That's right!
うん そ そうなの
Dinner's ready.
夕食 できてるぞ
Good!
Wait for me!
待って
This is relaxing!
Look, Bro!
いけ あんちゃん
Welcome!
"Young Tuna"
"Clams"
Kodaka, what are you making?
小鷹 何を作っている
Paella. You can buy
seafood cheaper at a port town.
パエリア 港のほうで魚介類が安く買えたからな
You even know how to make that kind of stuff?
そんなものまで作れるのか
Well, I've been living with
just Kobato for a long time now.
まあ 二人暮らしが長いからな
Isn't there any food that
you're good at cooking, Yozora?
夜空は得意な料理とかないのか
調理実習とかあったろ
You've had a cooking class, right?
ふん 調理実習のときはいつも部屋の隅でぽつんと立っていた
During the cooking class, I always
just stood alone in a corner of the room.
The jerks in my group would
cook as if I weren't there.
同じ班の連中は 私などいないかのように料理を作る
After they were finished making it,
they would put food on my plate,
作り終わったら 端っこの席について
お情けのように盛り付けられた 私の分の料理を気まずい思いをしながら食べるだけ
as if they felt pity for
the girl sitting on the end,
and I would eat it, embarrassed all the while.
I would always finish eating first,
then wash the dishes that I used.
And that's all I ever did in cooking class.
O-Oh...
Considering it was made
by Kodaka, this is really good.
真っ先に食べ終えて 自分の食べた分の食器を洗う
私が調理実習でやることはいつもそれだけだった
そ そうか
小鷹にしては上出来な味ね
It really is delicious!
ホント おいしいですね
今日は 一段と手によりをかけたではないか
Tonight's dinner is a step up from usual.
- I'm sure Aniki made this especially for us.
- Stupid poopy vampire!
バカなうんこ吸血鬼
Shut up! I...
うるさいばい うちは
- And now the weather...
- I guess tonight's the last of our training camp...
合宿も今晩で終わりか
Even though we're going home tomorrow,
明日には帰るってのに
we didn't really do any
training-camp-like things.
結局 合宿らしいことは何もしてないな
What's a training-camp-like thing?
合宿らしいことって何
海に向かって 「海だー！」と叫ぶ練習をしたじゃないか
We practiced yelling "The ocean!"
while facing the ocean, didn't we?
あれはノーカウントだろう
That doesn't count!
Certainly, Rika wants to
do a little something more.
確かに もうちょっと何かやりたいですね
だろ
Yeah, right?
Yes! When young men and
women gather together at night, they
はい 夜に若い男女が集まってやることといえば
そう 乱
have an or...
Don't be raunchy!
ひわいなことを言うな
Ow...
Then how about doing
something fitting for a summer night,
では 夏の夜らしく怪談とか肝試しとか どうでしょう
like telling ghost stories or a test of courage?
I'm surprised. I didn't expect
a science-oriented girl like you
意外だな バリバリ理系のお前がそういうこと言うとは
to say something like that.
女の子はみんなオカルト大好きなんですよ 先輩
All girls love the supernatural, Sempai.
Rika was an innocent girl
before she became a scientist.
理科も 科学者である前に 一人の乙女だったということです
But perverted.
痴女ですが
自分で言うなよ
Don't say that about yourself.
肝試しイベントは 「きらスク」でもあったから やってみたいわ
They had a test of courage in
Twinkle School, so I wanna try it too!
ふん ではみんなで怖い話を披露しあって
Then why don't we start
by sharing scary stories,
and then go to the forest outside?
それから外の林に行くのはどうだ
That's a good idea.
いいんじゃないか
As Aniki wishes...
アニキの望まれるままに
The dark of night is my friend.
夜の闇は わが朋友
恐怖など みじんも感じぬわ
I don't feel even a smidgen of fear...
わ 私だって お化けなんか怖くないぞ
I-I'm not scared of ghosts either!
All right...
では 言いだしっぺの理科から
We'll start with Rika, who had the idea.
I'm going to set the bar high at the start.
最初からハードル上げちゃいますよ
There was a book that looked
like "Ultra-Mecha" on the cover...
なんと 表紙はどう見てもフリデス本にしか見えないのに
...but when you opened it,
it said "Ultra-Magical" inside!
内容は デスフリ本だったのです
Hey. Are you gonna keep going?
おい 続きは
That's the end.
これで終わりですけど
Fine! Next.
はい 次
Then I'll go...
では 私が
"The Steamed Meat Dumpling Terror."
恐怖のしゅうまい
That's a funny story!
それは笑い話だ
しかし 本当に恐ろしい
But it really is scary...
次
Next!
I'm going to push you into the
deepest pit of terror with my scary story.
今度は 私の怪談で
あんた達を恐怖のどん底にたたき落としてやるわ
W-Why isn't anyone scared?
な 何でみんな怖がらないのよ
次
Next...
All right! I'll let you hear a ghost story
that I've been keeping in reserve.
よし それじゃあ俺がとっておきの怪談を聞かせてやる
The title is...
タイトルは「恐怖のみそ汁」
"The Miso Soup Terror."
く 苦しい
"I-It hurts!"
な なんでアウグスティヌス
"Wh-Why Augustinus?!
M-Mother, why did you put it in there?!"
お お母さん 何で入れた
何で入れたの アウグスティヌスの首
"Why did you put it in Augustinus' head?!"
何で笑うんだ
Why are you laughing?
Kodaka, why are you such a loser?
小鷹 何でお前はそう残念なのだ
Your story was...
あんたの話は
I don't understand your tastes.
お前らの感性は分からないぜ
Then we'll finish with my story
and move on to the test of courage.
では 私の話でおしまいにして
It's a story I heard from a friend...
これは私の友達から聞いた話だが
あんた 友達いないじゃない
But you don't have any friends...
黙れ 肉
Shut it, Meat!
Let's call the main
character of my tale..."Eiko."
物語の主人公の名前は仮にＡ子としておこう
She went to a public middle school.
とある公立中学に通う少女だった彼女には一人の親友がいた
She had one close friend.
The friend's name was...
let's see..."Waiko," we'll say...
名前は そうだな Ｙ子としておこう
Eiko and Waiko always did everything together.
Ａ子とＹ子は何をするにもいつも一緒だった
Meanwhile, there was a
ghost story about their school.
ところで 彼女達の学校には一つの怪談が伝えられていた
About a ghost called "Yamiko-san."
「闇子さん」と呼ばれる少女の霊だ
It was said that she would haunt
anyone who betrayed a friend at school,
彼女は学校で友達を裏切るようなまねをした人間にとりついて
and kill them.
殺してしまうのだという
One day, these girls started
competing over a boy they liked,
色恋沙汰による争いで 友情に亀裂が入って以来
and a crack formed in their friendship.
Eiko betrayed her former best friend, Waiko,
親友だったＹ子を裏切り いじめて自殺に追い込んだＡ子
bullied her, and drove her to suicide.
Then Eiko started noticing
supernatural phenomena all around her.
気がつくと Ａ子の周りには怪現象が起きるようになっていた
It continued to escalate...
それは どんどんエスカレートし続け
And then, at last...
そして ついに
Eiko vanished, never to be seen again.
それ以来 Ａ子の姿を見た者はいない
So, shall we do a test of courage?
さて 肝試しに行くか
Hey, Yozora, maybe we oughta call it a night...
なあ 夜空やっぱりやめないか
外は暗くて危ないし
It's dark out there, and dangerous...
そそそ そうよ
Th-Th-That's right! If anything
happened, we'd be in a real jam!
もしものことがあったら大変だし
では 肝試しは中止にするか
Then should we call off the test of courage?
After a while, Yozora's ghost story was
no longer so scary that I couldn't sleep.
時間がたってしまえば 夜空の怪談は怖くて眠れないってほどでもなかった
It was just the part about betraying
a best friend that stuck in my head.
ただ 親友を裏切ったって話が
俺の頭の中に引っかかっていた
He probably thinks I'm a traitor, too...
あいつも 俺を裏切り者だと思ってるんだろうか
It can't be!
まさか
Kodaka... Hey, Kodaka...
小鷹 ねえ 小鷹
Sena? What's wrong?
星奈 どうしたんだ
C-Come with me for a second.
ちょ ちょっとついてきて
What is it?
どうしたんだ
I-I want you to come with me to the bathroom.
ト トイレについてきてほしいの
The bathroom?
トイレ
I-It's not like I'm scared!
別に怖いわけじゃないんだからね
でも ほらあのね
But you know, just in case...
念のためっていうか
You should have Yozora go
with you. She's in the same room!
同じ部屋の夜空につきあってもらえばいいじゃないか
I'm sure she'd just make
fun of me if I asked her!
あいつにそんなこと頼んだら絶対バカにするでしょうが
Can we hurry? I can't hold it anymore...
早く ちょっとその限界だから
分かった
Yeah, sure...
You're there, right, Kodaka?
ちゃんといるわよね 小鷹
ああ いるぞ
Yeah, I'm here.
Kodaka, are you there?
小鷹 いる
I said I'm here...
You're there, right?!
いるわよね
いるって
I said I'm here!
ちゃんと返事してよ バカ
Answer me, idiot!
Kodaka, are you there?
小鷹 いる
I'm right here.
いるよ
Y-You'd better not tell Yozora about this.
よ 夜空に今のこと絶対言わないでよ
If you tell her, I won't forgive you!
言ったら許さないからね
Yeah, yeah.
Bro...
あんちゃん
What's wrong, Kobato?
どうした 小鳩
Go with me to the bathroom.
トイレ ついてきて
Bro, are you there?
あんちゃん おる
I'm here...
いるぞ
The bathroom?
トイレか
Oh! How did you know?
You're amazing, Big Brother!
おお 何で分かったのだ
おにいちゃんはすごいな
A-Are you there, Big Brother?!
おにいちゃん いる
うえッ おにいちゃん おにいちゃん
Big Brother! Big Brother!
いるぞ 安心して うんこしろ
I-I'm here! Relax and go poo!
分かった
Okay!
Yeah, yeah, let's go to the bathroom.
はいはい さっさとトイレ行くぞ
Huh? The bathroom?
はッ トイレ
Rika just came here to
crawl into bed with you...
理科はただ夜這いに来ただけですが
帰れ
Get out!
I should've gone myself before...
さっき自分のもしとけばよかった
W-What, Kodaka? What's wrong?
何だ 小鷹か どうしたのだ
I'm going to the bathroom!
トイレだよ
わ 私もトイレだ
M-Me too.
A-As long as we're both going,
let's go together, Kodaka.
せ せっかくだから 一緒に行くぞ 小鷹
Don't tell me you're scared
to go to the toilet yourself
お前 まさか闇子さんの話のせいで
because of the Yamiko-san story?
一人でトイレに行くのが怖いんじゃ
O-O-O-Of course not!
そそそ そんなことあるわけないだろう
Why are you scared of a story you came up with?
何で自分が話したネタで怖がってるんだよ
If the story didn't scare me, how could
I hope to scare other people with it?
自分が怖くない話で 他人を怖がらせられるわけないだろう
Um, Kodaka...
あ あの 小鷹
You can go first.
先 入っていいよ
Thanks.
すまん
K-Kodaka, you're there, right?
こ 小鷹いるな
I'm here...
いるよ
Kodaka?
小鷹
I'm here!
いる
I mean, I have to go too, so
there's no way I'm gonna leave.
つーか 俺もトイレ行きたいんだからいなくなるわけないだろう
Y-Yeah, that's right.
そ そうだな
Sorry to keep you waiting.
待たせたな
It's okay.
いや
I'll wait for you to finish too, Kodaka.
私も 小鷹が出るまで待っていてやろう
Kodaka, weren't you scared by that story?
というか 小鷹は怖くなかったのか あの怪談
Not at all.
全然 平気だ
I see... You weren't scared.
そうか 怖くなかったか
But... well...
でも まあ
It's not good to betray a friend, is it?
友達を裏切るのはよくないよな
Nope.
You're right.
そうだな
Aa, nounai souzou risou no genjitsu touhi
あー 脳內 想像理想の 現実逃避
今更どっちだっていっけど 友達作り
Ima sara docchi datte ikkedo... tomodachi zukuri
Hitori sabishii yatsu da to
sagesumu shisen ga ki ni naru
一人寂しい奴だと蔑む 視線が気になる
De, uwattsura dake atsumattara...
で 上っ面だけ集まったら
それでいいと 思っているうちに
Sore de ii to omotte iru uchi ni~
Are yo are yo to toujou, sorotte
あれよあれよと登場 揃って 破天荒な奴らに
Hatenkou na yatsura ni
Maipeesu midasarete yuku
マイペース 乱されてゆく 頭くる！特に憎っくき肉
Atama kuru! Toku ni nikukkuki niku!
Watashi no mune, hisoka
ni asette yuujou fudan kimi de
私の胸秘かに焦って 優柔不斷気味で
My heart tsutaerarenai
My heart 伝えられない 殘念なのは 私なのか
Zannen na no wa watashi na no ka?
Moya moya wo kakiwake Today!
もやもやを かきわけ Today！
Okizari ni sareta otome
gokoro ano hi kara kuyande iru
置き去りにされた 乙女心 あの日から悔やんでいる
Hayaku mitsuke dashite, maigo no kokoro
早く見つけ出して 迷子のココロ
By the way, with those ghost stories
before, I trailed behind you a bit, but...
ところで さっきの怪談では夜空にほんのわずかに遅れをとってしまった俺だが
Huh? What do you mean, a "bit"?
はあ どこがわずかだ
I think everyone knows that
when it comes to storytelling,
俺の話芸の本領は 実はお笑いにあるというのは誰でも知ってると思う
I'm skilled at funny stories.
I'd better get some sleep...
さっさと寝んとな
Wait a second!
What's with that sudden reaction?!
待て 何でいきなりそんな反応なんだよ
Don't you want to hear my comedic monologue?
俺の粋なお笑いトークを聞きたいとか思わんのか
Not in the least!
まったく思わん
せめて タイトルだけでも聞いて
At least hear the title!
寝る
I'm going to bed.
待て 待て 待て
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Next time: "Girls are Super Cute in Yukatas"!
"Next time: Girls are Super Cute in Yukatas"
次回 「女子は浴衣姿がな 超かわいい」
それじゃ次のタイトルはだな
So the next title is...
あれ 夜空 おい
Huh? Yozora? Hey!